{
    "subject": "resource/Mike_Simpson",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Washington_University_School_of_Dental_Medicine",
    "human_readable": "Mike Simpson attended Washington University School of Dental Medicine.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9854570031166077,
            "question": "Did Mike Simpson graduate from Washington University School of Dental Medicine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9772806763648987,
            "question": "What degree did Mike Simpson likely earn at Washington University School of Dental Medicine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9540942907333374,
            "question": "Where did Mike Simpson attend dental school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.945286214351654,
            "question": "Name the institution where Mike Simpson received his dental education."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9105246663093567,
            "question": "What is the name of the dental school that Mike Simpson attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9018945693969727,
            "question": "What type of medical school did Mike Simpson attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.815394401550293,
            "question": "Is Mike Simpson a dentist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7489174604415894,
            "question": "Is Washington University known for its dental school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7174153923988342,
            "question": "What field of medicine did Mike Simpson study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45808857679367065,
            "question": "What is Mike Simpson's profession based on his schooling?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mike Simpson attended Washington University School of Dental Medicine.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3344_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of medicine did Mike Simpson study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3344_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Washington University known for its dental school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3344_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mike Simpson a dentist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3344_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3344_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3344_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3344_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3344_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3344_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3344_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3344_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3344_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3344_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3344_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple, and Mike Simpson did attend Washington University School of Dental Medicine. This can be confirmed by checking multiple documents (#14, #22, #29) which mention his education at Washington University School of Dental Medicine."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently mention that Mike Simpson (also referred to as Michael Keith Simpson or simply Michael Simpson) attended the Washington University School of Dental Medicine in St. Louis, Missouri."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}